{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509579488","data":{"timestamp":" 947509579487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 74ddc8e1-61e3-4834-a234-d4964c7f69f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509587382","data":{"timestamp":" 947509587382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 74ddc8e1-61e3-4834-a234-d4964c7f69f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509587943","data":{"timestamp":" 947509587943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 74ddc8e1-61e3-4834-a234-d4964c7f69f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509607145","data":{"timestamp":" 947509607144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509607528","data":{"timestamp":" 947509607528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509607761","data":{"timestamp":" 947509607761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509608075","data":{"timestamp":" 947509608074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509608308","data":{"timestamp":" 947509608307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509611711","data":{"timestamp":" 947509611711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509612004","data":{"timestamp":" 947509612004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509612907","data":{"timestamp":" 947509612907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509613329","data":{"timestamp":" 947509613329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509616203","data":{"timestamp":" 947509616203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509616486","data":{"timestamp":" 947509616485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509617329","data":{"timestamp":" 947509617328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509617992","data":{"timestamp":" 947509617992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509618725","data":{"timestamp":" 947509618725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509619048","data":{"timestamp":" 947509619048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509619321","data":{"timestamp":" 947509619321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509619635","data":{"timestamp":" 947509619635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509619899","data":{"timestamp":" 947509619899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509623589","data":{"timestamp":" 947509623589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509623972","data":{"timestamp":" 947509623972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509624206","data":{"timestamp":" 947509624206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509624519","data":{"timestamp":" 947509624518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509624751","data":{"timestamp":" 947509624751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509628166","data":{"timestamp":" 947509628165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509628459","data":{"timestamp":" 947509628459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509629361","data":{"timestamp":" 947509629361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509629785","data":{"timestamp":" 947509629785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509632656","data":{"timestamp":" 947509632656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509632940","data":{"timestamp":" 947509632940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509633784","data":{"timestamp":" 947509633783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509634446","data":{"timestamp":" 947509634446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509635180","data":{"timestamp":" 947509635180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509635503","data":{"timestamp":" 947509635503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509635776","data":{"timestamp":" 947509635776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509636090","data":{"timestamp":" 947509636090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509636353","data":{"timestamp":" 947509636353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509639839","data":{"timestamp":" 947509639838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509639906","data":{"timestamp":" 947509639905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 122d1673-a44c-4b22-9853-86cf9ab29d35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509659356","data":{"timestamp":" 947509659356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a1a0cf8c-64a5-493d-9a50-d33d91d1de00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509659980","data":{"timestamp":" 947509659980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a1a0cf8c-64a5-493d-9a50-d33d91d1de00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509660223","data":{"timestamp":" 947509660223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a1a0cf8c-64a5-493d-9a50-d33d91d1de00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509660778","data":{"timestamp":" 947509660777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a1a0cf8c-64a5-493d-9a50-d33d91d1de00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509661921","data":{"timestamp":" 947509661921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a1a0cf8c-64a5-493d-9a50-d33d91d1de00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509662675","data":{"timestamp":" 947509662675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a1a0cf8c-64a5-493d-9a50-d33d91d1de00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509663750","data":{"timestamp":" 947509663749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a1a0cf8c-64a5-493d-9a50-d33d91d1de00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509663853","data":{"timestamp":" 947509663853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a1a0cf8c-64a5-493d-9a50-d33d91d1de00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509676678","data":{"timestamp":" 947509676678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 6ac4aeef-b578-4ea1-b4b2-5545027203f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509677301","data":{"timestamp":" 947509677301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 6ac4aeef-b578-4ea1-b4b2-5545027203f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509677544","data":{"timestamp":" 947509677543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 6ac4aeef-b578-4ea1-b4b2-5545027203f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509677726","data":{"timestamp":" 947509677725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 6ac4aeef-b578-4ea1-b4b2-5545027203f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509677821","data":{"timestamp":" 947509677821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 6ac4aeef-b578-4ea1-b4b2-5545027203f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509690376","data":{"timestamp":" 947509690376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 34bd0d0a-700a-43bf-984a-f22c59fb4071"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509690698","data":{"timestamp":" 947509690697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 34bd0d0a-700a-43bf-984a-f22c59fb4071"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509690788","data":{"timestamp":" 947509690788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 34bd0d0a-700a-43bf-984a-f22c59fb4071"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509711690","data":{"timestamp":" 947509711690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 044741ac-532a-4160-b236-65d31e6453e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_mka-me-vi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509720058","data":{"timestamp":" 947509720057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 044741ac-532a-4160-b236-65d31e6453e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_su-ngu-me"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509727779","data":{"timestamp":" 947509727778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 044741ac-532a-4160-b236-65d31e6453e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_vyi-wo-me"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509733134","data":{"timestamp":" 947509733134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 044741ac-532a-4160-b236-65d31e6453e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_me-to-ji"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509738952","data":{"timestamp":" 947509738951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 044741ac-532a-4160-b236-65d31e6453e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_me-mgo-ng'a"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509744616","data":{"timestamp":" 947509744616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 044741ac-532a-4160-b236-65d31e6453e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_do-me-mo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509750194","data":{"timestamp":" 947509750194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 044741ac-532a-4160-b236-65d31e6453e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_me-msa-de"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509755186","data":{"timestamp":" 947509755186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 044741ac-532a-4160-b236-65d31e6453e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_ga-me-ba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509761078","data":{"timestamp":" 947509761078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 044741ac-532a-4160-b236-65d31e6453e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_ga-me-ba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509767141","data":{"timestamp":" 947509767141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 044741ac-532a-4160-b236-65d31e6453e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_ga-me-ba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509775322","data":{"timestamp":" 947509775322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 044741ac-532a-4160-b236-65d31e6453e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_thi-njo-me"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509784936","data":{"timestamp":" 947509784936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 044741ac-532a-4160-b236-65d31e6453e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_mje-me-tu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509790714","data":{"timestamp":" 947509790711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" 044741ac-532a-4160-b236-65d31e6453e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_me_mje-me-tu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509812364","data":{"timestamp":" 947509812364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a9385a86-27a5-4c67-bfbd-fc62dec4646a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_me-be-ze"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509819577","data":{"timestamp":" 947509819577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a9385a86-27a5-4c67-bfbd-fc62dec4646a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_mche-me-vye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509829527","data":{"timestamp":" 947509829527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a9385a86-27a5-4c67-bfbd-fc62dec4646a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_me-je-be"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509836306","data":{"timestamp":" 947509836306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a9385a86-27a5-4c67-bfbd-fc62dec4646a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_bwe-de-me"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509844126","data":{"timestamp":" 947509844126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a9385a86-27a5-4c67-bfbd-fc62dec4646a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_ye-bwe-me"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509850188","data":{"timestamp":" 947509850188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a9385a86-27a5-4c67-bfbd-fc62dec4646a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_mre-kwe-me"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509855465","data":{"timestamp":" 947509855465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a9385a86-27a5-4c67-bfbd-fc62dec4646a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_ve-re-me"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509860684","data":{"timestamp":" 947509860684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a9385a86-27a5-4c67-bfbd-fc62dec4646a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_be-me-ge"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509865681","data":{"timestamp":" 947509865680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a9385a86-27a5-4c67-bfbd-fc62dec4646a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_nye-me-be"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509870167","data":{"timestamp":" 947509870167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a9385a86-27a5-4c67-bfbd-fc62dec4646a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_fe-ge-me"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" ge"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509876783","data":{"timestamp":" 947509876783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a9385a86-27a5-4c67-bfbd-fc62dec4646a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_fe-ge-me"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509882555","data":{"timestamp":" 947509882554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a9385a86-27a5-4c67-bfbd-fc62dec4646a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_me_fe-ge-me"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509899755","data":{"timestamp":" 947509899755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_160601"," gameId":" a9385a86-27a5-4c67-bfbd-fc62dec4646a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_me_fe-ge-me"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}